khaadionline.com 2014-01-30

# Khaadi - Privacy Policy

(Effective as of January 1, 2013)

Khaadi works to ensure that your privacy is protected when using our services. This website is operated by khaadi.com, and this privacy policy applies to your use of any of Khaadi’s websites using the domain khaadi.com .

We therefore have a policy explaining what personal information is, how we use the information, who has access to the data, and your rights regarding the information collected. Your access and use of our Website constitute your acceptance of our Privacy Policy and Terms of Use.

## Personal data

We take responsibility for all the personal data (such as your name, address, email address, phone number, and date of birth) that you provide us with, that we obtain when you subscribe to our newsletter or when you create a personal profile.

## How do we use your personal data?

We use the information that we collect to fulfill our commitments to you and to provide you with the service that you expect. This includes sending you information and offers for marketing purposes. In order to provide you with relevant offers and information, we may analyze your personal data. We will only keep your data for as long as necessary to carry out our services to you or for as long as we are required by law. After this your personal data will be deleted. 

## What information does khaadi.com share with third parties?

Khaadi may share your personal information with third parties or affiliates of Khaadi who perform services on our behalf or process authorized transactions. The personal information we share with these companies to perform services on our behalf is protected via contractual agreements and cannot be shared. We do not sell your information to any third party nor do we disclose your personal information to unaffiliated third parties.

## What are your rights?

You have the right to request information about the personal data we hold on you. If your data is incorrect, incomplete or irrelevant, you can ask to have the information corrected or removed.

## Cookies

A cookie is a small text file that is saved to, and, during subsequent visits, retrieved from your computer or mobile device. Khaadi uses cookies to enhance and simplify your visit. We do not use cookies to store personal information or to disclose information to third parties.

There are two types of cookies: permanent and temporary (session cookies). Permanent cookies are stored as a file on your computer or mobile device for no longer than 12 months. Session cookies are stored temporarily and disappear when you close your browser session.

We use permanent cookies to store your choice of start page and to store your details. We use session cookies when you use the product filtration function and to check if you are logged in. You can easily erase cookies from your computer or mobile device using your browser.

## Third-party cookies

We use third-party cookies to collect statistics in aggregate form in analysis tools such as Google Analytics and Core Metrics. The cookies used are both permanent and temporary cookies (session cookies). The permanent cookies are stored on your computer or mobile device for no longer than 24 months.
